This mother and child have come to the Synagogue Church Of All Nations with a strange predicament.
The medical report states that the young child had swallowed a foreign object,
that is now stuck in his small throat.
The question is: What object did he swallow?
Shockingly the x-ray of the one year old clearly shows a cross pendant securely lodged in his throat.
The presence of such a large foreign object in the throat of a one year old boy
must cause extreme discomfort and pain.
If the object is not removed, it could be fatal.
His mother has brought him to the SCOAN in desperate need of Divine intervention.
Let's hear what happened.
My name is Gift Stephen. I am coming from Ebonyi State.
The baby I am carrying is my baby, Meshak Stephen 1 year and five months.
Tell us the problem you have brought to the SCOAN today.
The problem that brought me here; is my baby swallowed a foreign object in the throat.
You mean your baby has a foreign object in his throat.
Yes.
He swallowed cross pendant. Since he swallowed the cross pendant, he doesn't sleep at night.
Even at night when we go to sleep, we sit till day break. He vomits.
The day when the cross enter his throat, he vomited blood.
When I carried him to the chemist, they told me that he swallowed a cross.
I then looked for my cross on my neck and I did not find the cross again
from the chain, but the chain was there but the cross - he swallowed the cross.
The cross is for me. The chain and pendant is my own.
Where have you taken him to for solution?
I took him to the chemist for the first one. I carried him to so many hospitals.
They told me that an operation will take it out.
And now that you are here in SCOAN today: What is your belief in Christ Jesus?
I believe Jesus will heal my son. In Jesus' name.
Amen
Healing Time
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer and deliverance to the people in Jesus' name.
Among them is young Meshek Stephen and his mother who cries to the man of God for help.
The lady is explaining that the baby she is holding swallowed a cross pendant as you can see in the x-ray.
So the cross pendant is now stuck to the throat of the baby.
There is never a problem Jesus Christ can not solve. And with a touch from Heaven, he is free.
Mrs Gift Stephen and Family. Prayer Line Testimony.
My name is Gift. The man that is behind me is my husband.
The problem that brought me to this place is this my boy.
He swallowed a cross pendant.
What is the name of your boy?
The name of my boy is Meshack Stephen.
He swallowed cross pendant when I was sleeping with him around five o'clock in the evening on Thursday.
The necklace hole was open. He now carried the thing and swallowed.
As he swallowed the cross pendant, I brought him to the chemistry.
The chemist now said I must carry him to the hospital. They said the thing is serious.
I carried him to hospital and they did an x-ray. The thing is there.
I carried him to another hospital. When we reached the hospital, the doctors said we should go for another x-ray.
we did the x-ray and came back. The thing was there. The thing was not shifted at all, it was there.
So I carried him to the same particular hospital.
They now directed me to the place where they could operate him on the neck to bring out the thing.
So we were confused, if it was ok to operate the boy.
Because it's my church well well. We didn't carry him to the hospital because we were confused.
We carried him to The SCOAN. As we reached The SCOAN, man of God now prayed for him.
He prayed for him and finished.
When I went to the house, the boy vomited.
The next day he started eating. But before the only thing he took was water.
Ok let us take it one by one so that people will understand what we saying.
So what happened to your son when he swallowed the pendant. Tell us what happened to your son?
When he swallowed the cross pendant, I was asleep.
When the boy was coughing and vomiting that's when I woke up.
And the boy vomited blood from his throat.
What did the boy do then?
He could not sleep and he was always crying.
When he was crying, he pointed at the throat to show me.
He was restless, he could not get himself.
What was he able to eat that time?
He could eat only tea, porridge and water.
And the mother further explained that when the boy ingested this metallic cross object,
that the boy could not eat then, that the only thing the boy could take was liquid things.
The man of God prayed for him. After he prayed for him, we went back to the house.
That night he vomited. After he vomited, we woke up in the morning. I gave him that tea.
He couldn't take the tea. He pointed at the pot. I gave him food which I cooked. He did not vomit it.
As the thing happened he started eating anything that he saw.
As he was eating, I now carried him to the hospital, went to the x-ray, we couldn't find the thing again.
Mrs Gift Stephen and Family Prayer Line Testimony
The mother further explained to the glory of God that after the prayer of man of God, Prophet T.B.Joshua,
that when they got home, the boy started vomiting and stooling. And when the vomiting stopped,
they found out the boy can eat normally. They noticed that boy started eating he saw around.
He started eating the food they gave to him. Unlike before that he could only take tea or anything liquid
because of the metallic cross that was blocking the esophagus. Even for him to swallow his own spit,
was a problem. But after the prayer, the boy was completely free.
And because the boy had started eating, they took the boy to the same hospital
that did the first x-ray and they conducted another x-ray and found out the object is no longer there.
That is what we are seeing on the screen right now.
Mrs Gift Stephen and Family Prayer Line Testimony
As you can see on the screen of your television set, that is the x-ray that was taken
after the prayer of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua that proved that indeed, the object
that was in the esophagus of the boy is no longer there.
My name is Stephen Ogazie and the woman beside me is my wife and my son, Mesheck.
We both came from Ebonyi State, Nigeria.
As a matter of fact, I thank God for what God has done.
I came back from work and I found out that the child was vomiting blood.
So, I asked my wife what was the matter. She told me that she was looking for her cross pendant.
When they did the first x-ray; the x-ray report was brought to the doctor. That was an object,
a cross pendant in the child's throat.
So, the surgeon doctor said that the only thing we should do - if we have such amount of money
like N300 000 to N400 000 before we can start any work.
So I then began to recall some certain things that the Lord is doing in this great commission.
So I knew fully well that the case of this child is just a cup case.
And I know fully well that if they had operated this child, they would not succeed
because that place is a major part of the body, is a worst part of the body.
So I know that if this child undergo operation he won't succeed.
So I began to give myself a second thought based on things that the Lord is doing on this great commission..
I said, if is it not better, if I run to God.
So we were opportuned, on the 9th of September, I came with my wife.
We were opportuned to meet the Man of God. The Man of God took the child,
and laid hand and prayed for the child. After that prayer he pronounced Liberty.
So I was surprised. As a matter of fact we went back home that day, the child vomited.
The vomiting increased. So I believed that the cross must have passed through this waste material.
Because he did not give us rest that night.
So after that night, the child began to eat every food.
Initially, he was only taking only liquid food, but he began to eat any kind of food.
He began to point to a particular food that we should bring for him.
So, I said, if this was the case, I now went back to the same surgeon doctor.
I said, " Sir there is something I want to verify." He said, "What is that?"
I said: "I want to run another test for this child."
He now agreed. He told me the price and we put the child on this machine and they ran the x-ray..
They brought the x-ray back. The man shouted.
He said: "Oga, what did you use to remove it?" I said: "I did not use anything, only prayer."
Mrs Gift Stephen and Family Prayer Line Testimony
So, I said I did not use anything but prayer!
He said: "Which kind of prayer would remove this thing?
Even the operation which you wanted to conduct, was not even enough.
We know how it is, only a professional doctor can touch that joint of a child."
I said we went to SCOAN. The man shouted. I said I came to SCOAN for prayer.
And my child was privileged to receive prayer from Man Of God and from that day the child got free.
So he said: "No problem." He ran the test, everything from the neck down to the sole of the feet of the child -
he could not find anything again - body, abdomen.
He now said: "Is this magic?" I said there is no magic because if not Jesus...
So the man said: "Thank God because this thing God has done to you - no man will ever do it.
this thing God has done to you - no man..."
He said this is the only case where God will visit you.
The man never agreed with me, he asked wether I used something to bring out the cross.
He said he did not see any sore, any sign of pain, any sign of sore.
I said there is nothing like that, it's just prayer. The man of God laid hand and prayed - that's the end.
And advised us with all manner of confidence that the case is settled.
The doctor himself was surprised. - He was surprised. He asked where is that place. I said this is SCOAN .
Shall will put our hands together for the Lord Jesus.
What seemed impossible with men is absolutely possible with God Almighty.
And we have seen evidence that proves beyond reasonable doubt.
If not God what do we think could have happened to this little boy?
But we give glory to God Almighty for this wonderful miracle that God has brought in the life of...
So tell us what has been the condition of your son ever since then?
The condition of the child right from the day the Man of God prayed for him, there was no atom
of vomition again. The child have been free from every stress. The child sleeps well, we hardly wake him.
He sleeps well, he feels free, he plays all around. He takes any food.
So because of this thing, of this freedom we determined to go again for second x-ray.
Which we did, and the child has plain abdomen - the cross is no longer there.
So I now met the doctor and said, I wanted to run another x-ray.
So for a practical evidence. The man said, he runs the same x-ray, and showed me on the screen.
He said there is no need of printing it out because the case is settled, I should just go and give glory to God.
Mr Stephen Ogazie and Family Prayer Line Testimony
I just appreciate God. The first place here; is the place we went to the hospital and we were refereed to
another hospital because the surgeon doctor...
Let's start from the top so that we can understand.
This is one is just a report, the first x-ray report.
The first x-ray report here shows the child has an object in the lungs.
Then the second x-ray report - the same thing happened, the same picture was there, the same cross was still there.
Then the third one, this very one you see here - was just a referred letter to different hospitals.
Then this one is the final x-ray report that we did, that we brought to the doctor.
And the doctor pronounced that he had not seen anything from the body of the child anymore.
From this area. So we had to run the test from the throat down to the abdomen and could not find the cross anymore.
So the man said we should give thanks to God that this matter is settled.
That no man can do this except God.
So what we are seeing on the board is the before and the after.
Shall we put our hands together for the Lord Jesus Christ.
Just down there we can also see an x-ray; can you just tell us more about the x-ray we seeing there?
Yes. This first place here was the first x-ray, the diagnosis history. The first x-ray report here.
Then the second one here; is the second x-ray report the doctor said he want to compare the both,
to know whether the cross was still on the same position. We went to the lab test.
and we brought the second x-ray. Then the last one here...
Just take it one after the other so that people can understand. We have three x-rays there,
the first one we are seeing there is the first x-ray that was conducted.
And they found out that the boy ingested a metallic cross object that we are seeing right there,
on the esophagus of the boy before they came to SCOAN.
And after the prayer of the Man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua
they went to the same hospital, conducted another test, ran an x-ray and that's what we are seeing
on the right hand side and find out that the boy is perfectly ok
and the object is no longer there.
The word of advice I'm giving to everyone, the world at large and the people viewing us,
watching the SCOAN service. The advice I'm giving to you is that: no matter the challenges and oppositions
of life, you are facing, no matter the temptations no matter the tests -
God is the last bus stop, always seek Him and always believe in Him.
Because it is not he that wrote your first letter that will ever determine your final results.
But He who will write your final letter will determine your final results and that person is Jesus Christ.
Indeed, Jehovah has the final say. Shall we put our hands together for the Lord Jesus Christ.
What I want to tell the mothers is: when something happens to you like this, trust in God.
God can do anything. And even when you carry baby in your hands, be careful and watchful for the baby.
That was word of advice from madam Gift Stephen. Now we want to encourage the family.
That now the Lord has set your son free; as the Scripture says: "As for me and my family, we will serve the Lord."
We want you and your family to go and serve the Lord, in Spirit and in truth
and train the child in the way of the Lord. And we pray that God Almighty will grant you and your family,
the grace to do so, in Jesus' name.
Once again shall we put our hands together for the miracle working God.
TT Monica Asefa 25/07/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 31/07/2018